1websdirectory.com 2017-11-21

# Privacy Policy - 1WebsDirectory.com

1 Webs Directory understands and respects your concerns about privacy. It is requested however, that you provide information about yourself in order for us to be able to understand your needs and requirements better and make the experience at 1 Webs Directory more valuable and enriching for you. The Privacy Policy is to inform or notify you about the information needed by us and how the information provided by you may be shared with third parties and how it is important for the proper operation of the website. This Privacy Policy is subject to the Terms and Conditions posted on the Site, including the provisions regarding change or modification of this Privacy Policy and other policies as set forth in the Terms and Conditions. You have the responsibility of regularly checking the policy to be updated about the changes and modifications made to the Privacy Policy. Use of the website after the changes to the Privacy Policy have been made will be considered as acceptance of the changes. This Privacy Policy is part of, and incorporated into, the Terms and Conditions.

#### Information we collect:

**Submission**

Information from our users is important to ensure a satisfying experience at 1 Webs Directory. The submit form must be duly completed with contact information like name and email and other details as required. The information provided is used to contact users regarding the services for which the user has shown express interest.

####  Uses of Information:

**Profile**

The information collected is stored in the form of log files. The information collected through the submit form is used to create a complete profile of the users. The profile provides us with all the information required to serve you better and make this a satisfying experience. The profile thus, created with the information is not shared with third parties.

#### Log Files

Like most standard web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

#### Communications from the Site:

**Special Offers and Updates**

There would be regular updates of new services launched and special deals or offers provided from time to time to our established users. The privacy of our users is top priority and thus, we provide the option to the users to receive or not receive these updates and special offers.

#### Service Announcements

In some cases which is very rare, it becomes necessary for us to forward information related to our service like maintenance of the site for which the service is suspended. For such purposes we may use the email for informing our users. These are not promotional and the users are thus, not provided the option of opting out of them.

#### Sharing

**Legal Disclaimer**

We take all care and precaution to protect the privacy of our users, however, we may need to disclose personal information if and when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

#### Third Party Intermediaries

2Checkout is the service used by us for billing the users for the services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

#### Links to Other Sites

1 Webs Directory has no control over the sites that are linked to here and that come up in the search results. These sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. 1 Webs Directory assumes no responsibility or liability for the same and you are requested to scrutinize their Privacy Policy and remove any cookies from your computer if you have any concerns.

#### Security

We take every precaution and care to protect the information provided by our users. The information and data provided by users via the website is both online and off-line. 

#### Additional Information:

1 Webs Directory reserves the right to make changes to the privacy policy at any point of time and thus, it is requested that you do make regular checks to be up to date with the changes.

Any questions relating to this privacy policy may be sent through our contact page.
